>> Brian Holt: 好的，我们去找 ref.js.
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Okay, let's go to ref.js.
在我看来，这是开始变得艰难的地方。
So this is where, in my opinion,
this starts getting hard.
因此，我在此处具有此 useRef 示例，如果单击了延迟日志记录。
So I have this useRef example here and
if I click delay logging.
>> Brian Holt: 注意它说，你可以看到它上面写着，
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Notice that it says,
you can see right there it says,
一个引用一个引用
state one ref one.
但注意警戒状态是零引用号
But notice this says in the alert,
state zero ref one, okay?
我想在此显示延迟日志记录中的增量，而延迟日志记录是
And I want to show you here increments in
delay logging which is the function that's
其实是在提高警觉对吧
actually doing the alert, right?
>> Brian Holt: 设置状态，我立即调用该状态，我说设置状态加上一个，
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: The set state, I call that
right away and I say set state plus one,
对吧 ?
right?
我说 numRef current plus plus ，您将假定状态号和
And I say numRef current plus plus,
you would assume that state number and
因为它们总是处于锁定的阶段对吧
current because they're always
kept in locked step, right?
请在此处使用状态和使用引用，它们都从零开始
Use state and use ref right here,
they both start at zero and
都是同时递增的
they're both incremented at the same time.
他们也会是一样的对吧
They would be the same always, right?
那么他们为什么不一样呢 ?
So why aren't they the same?
> > Brian Holt: 这就是你遇到的问题，
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Well this is kind
of the problem that you run into,
这是个了结的问题吧
this is a problem with a closure, right?
如果你不了解关闭的好情况凯尔 - 辛普森有个不错的课程
And if you don't understand closure super
well, Kyle Simpson has a great course on
在Fron趋向大师赛上肯定是这样
it in Frontend Masters, so
definitely check that out.
但足以说明这里的国家数字并没有改变。
But suffice to say that stateNumber
here actually doesn't change.
因此，我正在设置状态号，并且正在递增，
So I am setting stateNumber,
and it is incrementing,
导致重新呈现，对吗 ?
and it is causing a re-render, right?
因此当我单击延迟日志记录时，请注意状态和
So when I click delay logging,
notice that state and
裁判都变了对吧
ref both change immediately, right?
但是之前的迭代的状态号没有改变，对吧 ?
But this state number from the previous
iteration has not changed, right?
这个封闭装置就在这个状态号上，对吧 ?
And this closure is holding
onto this state number, right?
所以实际注销的是先前版本的状态号。
So what's actually getting logged out is
the previous version of the state number.
如果我再点击两次会发生什么
Watch what happens if I click it twice.
>> Brian Holt: 2 和 4，对吗 ?
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Two and four, right?
原因是它正在从 numRef.current 中读出
And the reason being is it's reading
out of numRef.current, that's always
将会是确切的时间，这就是 numRef的值。
going to be the exact moment in time,
this is what that numRef's value is.
状态号的 stateRef 始终被保存在前一个上，
Whereas stateRef for the state number is
always being held onto the previous one,
因为关闭了那个状态
because of the closure
holding onto that state.
>> Brian Holt: 这是否有意义 ?
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Does that make sense?
>> Brian Holt: 这一背景不同的原因是我们正在
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: And the reason why this
context is being different is cuz we're
在未来进行设定的时间和日志记录。
doing a set time out and
logging in the future.
>> Brian Holt: 这就是 Refs 的用途。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: This is
what Refs are used for.
它们很有用，因为它们允许你，如果你有问题的话，
They're useful because they allow you, if
you have a problem, where you have these
多个关闭问题，您需要在这些问题上保持同一状态。
multiple closure problems where you
need to hold on to the same state.
也许这个 useRef 总是正确的正确的
Maybe it's very important that this
useRef be always the exact right one and
在任何情况下都可以调用它。
it can be called in any context.
那就是你想用 Ref 的时候吧
That's when you would want to use a Ref,
right?
因此，如果您正在执行类组件，那么只会创建实例变量
So if you were doing a class component,
you would just make an instance variable
在课堂上我们是这样处理的对吧
in the class, and
that's how we would handle that, right?
这就是我们以前在 React 中处理的方式
That's how we've always
handled that before in React,.
但我们不再有这种能力了，因为这不再是一个阶级，
But we don't have that ability anymore
because this is no longer a class,
是一种功能对吧
it's a function, right?
因此 useRef 允许我们这样做。
So useRef allows us to do that.
所以 useRef 所做的就是给你这个东西。
So what useRef does is it
gives you this object.
这个物体有一个叫做电流的东西。
And this object has exactly one
thing on it called current.
如果我试了也会出错
It actually will error if I try and
表示 numRef.thelse 等于 5。
say numRef.something else equals five.
它说，这个对象是不可扩展的。
It says hey,
this object is not extensible.
实际上，它实际上限制了你只使用电流。
So it actually literally limits
you to only use current.
> > Brian Holt: 如果我说电流，那就会消失，好吗 ?
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: If I say current,
that'll go away, okay?
它们通过密封物体来做到这一点。
They do that by sealing the object.
>> Brian Holt: 有关 Refs的问题 ?
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Questions about Refs?
>> Brian Holt: 这对于
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: So this'll be useful for
喜欢经常保持在 DOM 元素上的东西。
things like holding onto
DOM elements frequently.
它也很有用的保持时间和时间间隔
It's also useful holding onto timeouts and
holding onto intervals so
你可以确保你得到的是正确的
you can make sure that
you get the correct one.